Please, please.
من فضلك من فضلك.
-Let's do it. -Okay.
-دعنا نقوم به.  -تمام.
Come on, let's do it
هيا دعونا نفعل ذلك
After you
بعدك
Thank you, Master Cheng, for your help.
شكرا لك سيد تشنغ على مساعدتك.
Let's have a toast.
دعونا لها نخب.
Come on, drink it.
تعال ، اشربه.
My brother,
أخي،
it's all up to you this time.
الأمر كله متروك لك هذه المرة.
That's why we can save the Liu Army.
لهذا السبب يمكننا إنقاذ جيش ليو.
How can I repay you.
كيف يمكنني أن أرد لك.
Miss Liu Zhi,
ملكة جمال ليو تشي ،
it's easy.
من السهل.
Don't mention it.
لا تذكرها.
Why didn't you
لماذا لم تفعل
invite Miss Su up the mountain?
دعوة ملكة جمال سو أعلى الجبل؟
Lake fishing business is so good,
تجارة صيد البحيرة جيدة جدًا ،
she can't leave alone.
لا يمكنها المغادرة بمفردها.
Am I right?
هل انا على حق؟
Miss Liu Zhi,
ملكة جمال ليو تشي ،
drink less,
اشرب اقل
Moderate drinking can ease one's mind.
يمكن للشرب المعتدل أن يريح المرء.
My brother,
أخي،
Eldest Brother,
أكبر الإخوة،
What should I call you if you like?
ماذا يجب أن اتصل بك إذا أردت؟
I think whatever you call it is easy to say.
أعتقد أنه من السهل قول كل ما تسميه.
It's so tangled.
انها متشابكة جدا.
You can call me whatever you want.
يمكنك الاتصال بي ما تريد.
Whatever.
أيا كان.
How can you save
كيف يمكنك حفظ
the entire Liu Army at will?
جيش ليو بأكمله في الإرادة؟
For the rest of my life,
لبقية حياتي،
when I'm a cow or a horse,
عندما أكون بقرة أو حصان
I want to repay you.
اريد ان اعيد لك.
I didn't do it all by myself.
لم أفعل كل ذلك بنفسي.
It's all thanks to you.
كل الشكر لك.
Right, Advisor?
أليس كذلك مستشار؟
This is six,
هذه ستة
Advisor,
مستشار ،
it's no big deal.
ليس بالأمر الجلل.
It's not a big deal.
لا مشكلة.
If I hadn't risked my life
إذا لم أخاطر بحياتي
to fight with Du Mao.
للقتال مع دو ماو.
If the Seven Arrests and Seven Arbiters strategize,
إذا كانت استراتيجية الاعتقالات السبعة والحكام السبعة ،
they might lose this battle.
قد يخسرون هذه المعركة.
Come on.
تعال.
Remember that battle in Falling Leaf City,
تذكر تلك المعركة في Falling Leaf City ،
Du Mao used a good mace.
استخدم دو ماو صولجانًا جيدًا.
I, the jade-faced scholar Xu Shenji, don't belittle him.
أنا ، الباحث ذو الوجه اليشم Xu Shenji ، لا تستخف به.
When the battle came to a head,
عندما وصلت المعركة إلى ذروتها ،
I only saw my luck in the Dantian,
رأيت فقط حظي في دانتيان ،
His figure is elegant,
شخصيته أنيقة ،
using the secret method of lost transmission of Xu family,
باستخدام الطريقة السرية للانتقال المفقود لعائلة Xu ،
They are neck and neck,
هم العنق والرقبة ،
Okay
تمام
A cosy young man.
شاب دافئ.
Congratulations on completing
مبروك على الانتهاء
all the tasks of running Toad Village,
جميع مهام تشغيل قرية العلجوم ،
What's the next task?
ما هي المهمة التالية؟
Let's talk about it after I wake up.
دعنا نتحدث عنها بعد أن أستيقظ.
The system still needs to sleep,
لا يزال النظام بحاجة إلى النوم ،
and upgrading Toad Village by hand is very hard,
وترقية قرية العلجوم باليد أمر صعب للغاية ،
For a long time,
لفترة طويلة،
you won't be able to see me anymore.
لن تتمكن من رؤيتي بعد الآن.
Don't miss me too much.
لا تفتقدني كثيرا.
If you don't have a task,
إذا لم يكن لديك مهمة ،
you can sleep late.
يمكنك النوم متأخرا.
Miss Liu Zhi,
ملكة جمال ليو تشي ،
my brother,
أخي،
What are you
ما أنت
doing?
عمل؟
I'm sorry,
أنا آسف،
my brother,
أخي،
Ever since the brothel saved me that day,
منذ أن أنقذني بيت الدعارة ذلك اليوم ،
Liu Zhi's heart
قلب ليو تشي
has been in my brother's hands.
كان بين يدي أخي.
From now on,
من الان فصاعدا،
let me
دعني
stay by your side.
ابق بجانبك.
I'm sorry,
أنا آسف،
Miss Liu Zhi,
ملكة جمال ليو تشي ،
I know what you mean.
أنا أعرف ما تعنيه.
But I already
لكني بالفعل
have someone in my heart.
لدي شخص ما في قلبي.
Well,
حسنًا،
love can't be forced.
الحب لا يمكن إجباره.
Am I right?
هل انا على حق؟
Do you understand what I mean?
هل تفهم ما أقصد؟
Hey,
يا،
I can't even sleep late.
لا أستطيع حتى أن أنام متأخرًا.
You really have the heart to plant flowers but they won't bloom.
لديك حقًا قلب لزراعة الزهور لكنها لن تتفتح.
Wu Xin,
وو شين ،
Su Ying,
سو ينغ ،
Now the restaurant is on the right track,
الآن المطعم يسير على الطريق الصحيح ،
why don't you come back to Toad Village with me.
لماذا لا تعود معي إلى قرية العلجوم.
I'm just kidding.
أنا أمزح.
I know you can't live without Falling Leaf City now,
أعلم أنه لا يمكنك العيش بدون Falling Leaf City الآن ،
and the restaurant business
وأعمال المطاعم
is on the right track now.
يسير على الطريق الصحيح الآن.
Why are you willing to leave,
لماذا أنت على استعداد للمغادرة ،
the landlady?
صاحبة الارض؟
Am I right?
هل انا على حق؟
Then I'll come back to see you when I have time.
ثم سأعود لرؤيتك عندما يكون لدي الوقت.
Yes.
نعم.
Cheng Dalei,
تشنغ دالي ،
will you really come?
هل ستاتي حقا